{
    "id": "d6610c35beab439c8540d1d6612dbc94",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The boy walked ——————– the road.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "along",
                "on",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8175bdbec6044493be30a545fe051456"
        },
        {
            "question": "The river flows ——————- the bridge.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "below",
                "under",
                "through"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "588d5561014b42d5866f82a04f389331"
        },
        {
            "question": "The work was done —————– haste.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5f90585948494cefb384c5b15e2c158b"
        },
        {
            "question": "He died —————– his country.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "on",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "dd75e8e57f894ea88246ee19604b06cd"
        },
        {
            "question": "The steam engine was invented —————— James Watt.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "by",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0e86f9316423456d954bf362e551ec45"
        },
        {
            "question": "The robbers jumped —————– the compound wall.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "across",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "712b8d7c6c484db19e0f57dfb6db10bd"
        },
        {
            "question": "The village was destroyed —————— fire.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "by",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1b330928814a4803a5aade9c85383506"
        },
        {
            "question": "He spoke —————- me —————— French.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with, in",
                "to, in",
                "at, in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "738508470f1d40c5b85e3aa75028a61e"
        },
        {
            "question": "They live —————— the same roof.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "under",
                "within"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6efd08b1ddec4034bb55eb0bb5a5ee98"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have not seen him ——————– last Wednesday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "since",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d039aa2f0d08497d9a138f8e7d3ed3a3"
        }
    ]
}